Preliminary Guide to The Thomas Hahn Chesapeake and Ohio Canal collection, 1939-1993 MS2020
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Canal boats on water next to a white shed. n.d., undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Cushwa's Williamsport., 1920 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Conococheague Aqueduct and Creek with Potomac River, Cushwa's Basin Williamsport, MD, undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Men working on the canal at Conococheague Aqueduct and Creek, Cushwa's Basin, Williamsport, MD. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Darby Grain Mill. Williamsport. Mr. Darby in door of mill. Mill burned in 1904., 1890 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- C&O Canal freight boat number 43 after it breached the berm parapet wall of the Conococheague Aqueduct and plunged into Conccocheague Creek, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Williamsport aqueduct above Lock 44 over Conococheaque Creek looking toward the Potomac River. Showing clearing, missing handrail and needed masonry work. December, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Berm side of the Conococheague Aqueduct., 1939 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Aqueduct. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Williamsport Aqueduct above Lock 44 looking upstream after clearing of brush. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Aqueduct. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Williamsport Aqueduct above Lock 44 looking downstream, showing clearing and new foot bridge. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Williamsport Aqueduct above Lock 44, over Conococheaque Creek looking upstream of creek. Showing after clearing, missing handrail and needed painted up of masonry. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 55)
- Jarboe's Store at Edward's Ferry Lock., ca. 1962 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Building near Lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper II" at Lock 20, Potomac, MD. n.d, ca. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 58)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper II" preparing to ext Lock 6, Washington DC., ca. 1962 (Box 20, Folder 59)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper II" on Level 4, Washington, DC. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Excursion Boat "Canal Clipper I" entering Lock 5 at Brookmont MD. July 27, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper I" entering Lock 5, Brookmont, MD. July 27, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper II" beneath Key Bridge in Georgetown. August 8, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 63)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper II" Level 4, Washington DC. July 8, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Dummy freighter (prop that was used in film "Canals West") in Lock 5, Brookmont, MD. April 26, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 65)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper I" on Widewater, Potomac, MD. July 27, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 66)
- Excursion boat, "Canal Clipper II" Level 4, Washington DC. August 8, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 67)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper II" exiting Lock 20, Potomac, MD., ca. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 68)
- Locks on the Rideau Canal., 1840 (Box 20, Folder 69)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad train and canal freighter near Sandy Hook, MD., ca. 1900 (Box 20, Folder 70)
- Excursion steamboat "Louise of Georgetown" near Great Falls Tavern and Lock 20, Potomac MD., 1902-1910 (Box 20, Folder 71)
- Excursion boat "John Quincy Adams" on Level 20, Potomac MD. August 31, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 72)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper III" approaching Lock 20, Potomac MD., ca. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 73)
- Excursion motorboat with "Chesapeake Canoe" hull, U.S. Geological Survey employees on an outing along the C&O Canal, 1914-1916 (Box 20, Folder 74)
- People on a canal barge. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 75)
- Canal Towage Company Boat number 34, Williamsport, MD after 1936 flood, undated (Box 20, Folder 76)
- Bow of barge number 57 below Hancock., 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 77)
- Rock Creek with Pennsylvania Ave. bridge in the background, scow dredge freighter in Tide Lock Level. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 78)
- Excursion motorboat "Viking" at Lock 24, Seneca, MD., ca. 1915 (Box 20, Folder 79)
- Midship section of Barge number 57 below Hancock., 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 80)
- Freighter No. 73 in Conococheague Creek after having crashed through the Conococheague Aqueduct, Williamsport MD. April, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 81)
- Excursion motor boat in Lock., 1900-1920 (Box 20, Folder 82)
- Great Falls Tavern, canoers leaving Lock 20, Potomac MD, 1900-1920 (Box 20, Folder 83)
- Abandoned scow and dredge., 1930s (Box 20, Folder 84)
- Along the Potomac River looking down the canal from intake lock., 1900-1920 (Box 20, Folder 85)
- Canal boat. East from Lock 12. August 29, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 86)
- Boaters on the canal at either Lock 12 or 14. early 1900's, undated (Box 20, Folder 87)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper I" near Washington, DC. July 27, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 88)
- Excursion boat "Canal Clipper II" Level 3, Washington DC. October 23, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 89)
- Excursion boat Canal Clipper I Level 4, near Washington, DC. July 31, July 31, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 90)
- Excursion boat Canal Clipper I near Washington, DC. July 27, July 27 1941 (Box 20, Folder 91)
- Train and canal boat. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 92)
- Map of the country between Washington and Pittsburg referring to the contemplated Chesapeake and Ohio Canal and its general route and profile. October, 1826 (Box 20, Folder 93)
- NCP office party, C&O Canal barge trip. Canal Clipper I going under Key Bridge in Georgetown. September 9, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 94)
- Map of C&O Canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 95)
- Map of C&O Canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 96)
- Map of C&O Canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 97)
- Fuder Canal, Dam number 6. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 98)
- Canal boat and railroad. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 99)
- Forrest-Marbury Mansion. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 100)
- Dried up and overgrown lock with house in background. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 101)
- Canal boat on the C&O Canal., 1900-1920 (Box 20, Folder 102)
- Canal Towage number 35 and 51 canal boats. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 103)
- Lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 104)
- Lock house B on the Washington (Eastern) Branch of the C&O Canal., 1860 (Box 20, Folder 105)
- Lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 106)
- Lock house on canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 107)
- Lock 74 Pittsburgh Glass Company area. Looking upstream. Shows clearing of structure only. March 16, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 108)
- Rowboat "Mamie" at Lock 6., 1880s (Box 20, Folder 109)
- US senator Charles McC. Mathias, Jr. of Maryland, inspects an impressionistic painting of the Seneca Aqueduct., 1978 (Box 20, Folder 110)
- 2 canal boats on canal with smaller boat on the right. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 111)
- Bypass flume at Lock 19. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 112)
- Great Falls Tavern. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 113)
- Lock house 22. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 114)
- Locks on the Rideau Canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 115)
- The Ottawa River at Bytown. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 116)
- The Rideau Canal, Bytown. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 117)
- Boat making was an important industry in Cumberland. Here at the boat yard two boats are in progress on the ways and another is awaiting finishing touches prior to be placed into commission. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 118)
- Demolition team setting charges in Dam number 8. Cumberland, MD. C&O Canal. April 12, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 119)
- Lock 70 Oldtown. Showing lock house and cleared towpath. March 16, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 120)
- Lock 71. Oldtown Sportsman's Club. After clearing of structure. March 16, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 121)
- Pump house and lock on 8 mile level above Oldtown MD. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 122)
- Lock 72. Blue Spring Patterson Creek. Looking upstream below lock. Shows clearing of structure. March 16, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 123)
- Lock 72 Blue Spring.Looking upstream. After clearing of underbrush from Canal bed and towpath. April 27, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 124)
- A "Short Level" between Lock 73 and Lock 74. Railroads crossed the canal many times between Georgetown and Cumberland, this crossing being Bridge 65 of the B&O Railroad., 1907-1923 (Box 20, Folder 125)
- Sideling Hill Creek Aqueduct from downstream side, east bank of Sideling Hill Creek above Lock 56. Showing railroad bridge upstream of the Aqueduct, before clearing. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 126)
- mile below Little Orleans on towpath, Lock 57. Showing clearing of canal bed and towpath and brush piled for clearing. October 18, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 127)
- Little Orleans Aqueduct below Lock 58. Showing down stream face after undergrowth removed. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 128)
- Little Orleans Aqueduct looking downstream below Lock 58. After clearing completed shows masonry work and missing handrail. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 129)
- Lock 69 in the foreground and Lock in the background. Looking upstream. After clearing of structure and towpath. March 16, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 130)
- Feeder lock gate at Dam number 6 east of Pearee, MD opposite Capacon. Lock 55. Looking downstream showing missing retaining wall after removal of undergrowth. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 131)
- Remains of Dam 6 near Great Cacapon, WV, undated (Box 20, Folder 132)
- Dam six from the Maryland side and Great Cacapon. October 17, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 133)
- Stone work. October 14, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 134)
- Falls, possibly Dam 6 near Great Cacapon, West Virginia. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 135)
- Lock 55 Dam 6. Looking into feeder lock from downstream side. After clearing. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 136)
- Dam 5 near Clear Spring, MD., undated (Box 20, Folder 137)
- Dam number 6. Poly Pond on the right. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 138)
- Sideling Hill Creek Aqueduct. 2 miles downstream from Little Orleans. Looking from railroad tressel into aqueduct from the west side. Above Lock 58. After clearing. Wall over barrel missing on upstream side. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 139)
- Lock 631/3 Downstream from Paw Paw Tunnel. Partial clearing of structures. Lock 631/3, one of the three locks concentrated just below the Paw Paw Tunnel. Note the rough rubble stone used in the construction of the lock walls as an 'economy measure'. October 18, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 140)
- View of the cut below the Paw Paw Tunnel from the interior of the tunnel., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 141)
- Hikers in the Paw Paw Tunnel. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 142)
- Paw Paw Tunnel. Downstream side. Taken form an old postal card. Almost all former boatmen had something to say about the Paw Paw Tunnel. This view shows the wooden towpath at the downstream end of the tunnel. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 143)
- Paw Paw Tunnel. Showing restoration of masonry work. October 18, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 144)
- Paw Paw Tunnel. Brick work restoration. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 145)
- Paw Paw Tunnel. Downstream entrance. Preliminary clearance of portals. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 146)
- Paw Paw Tunnel masonry restoration. The Paw Paw Tunnel requires frequent attention to keep it in a safe condition for hikers and bikers to pass through. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 147)
- Canal boat on canal at Pinesburg Station., 1920 (Box 20, Folder 148)
- Lock on canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 149)
- Dam 5 near Clear Spring, MD. "Canal boats used the river for navigation for about a half mile in the slackwater behind Dam 5, called "Little Slackwater." On one occasion a boat was swept over this dam and the captain and his daughter were killed." n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 150)
- Lock number 5. Mule Bridge and Foot Bridge. Locktenders Watch House., 1906 (Box 20, Folder 151)
- Lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 152)
- Canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 153)
- Slackwater above dam 5. Upstream end of cut at Little Slackwater., 1906 (Box 20, Folder 154)
- Great Falls Tavern., 1920 (Box 20, Folder 155)
- Shenandoah Outlet Lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 156)
- Drawing of the approach by canal to Lock 33 (Harpers Ferry Lock ) by Lieutenant Washington Hood in 1832. n.d., undated (Box 20, Folder 157)
- Chesapeake and Delaware Removal of old lock at Ches. City. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 158)
- Harper's Ferry, WV. "The Shenandoah River Outlet Lock was located just to the left in this photograph. Boats were poled across the Potomac River to the mouth of the Shenandoah River at the far end of the Bollman truss bridge to Harpers Ferry, which is shown in the background.", late 1800s (Box 20, Folder 159)
- Approaching Lock 33. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 160)
- Probably the arch of the former Potomac Aqueduct Bridge spanning Water St. in Georgetown, DC., undated (Box 20, Folder 161)
- Probably a C&O canal basin at Cumberland, MD. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 162)
- Mole Bridge-above dams-2 Locks., 1900 (Box 20, Folder 163)
- Along the canal at villages, or important agricultural districts, or where valleys break through the mountains, there were warehouses where mule feed and other boat stores including bread could be procured, and where goods could be received and delivered by the boats. Photo is of Four Locks where such service were obtained. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 164)
- Lock, footbridge and buildings. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 165)
- Lock 61. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 166)
- Supreme Court Justice William O .Douglas on the C&O Canal., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 167)
- C&O Canal hike. April, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 168)
- Canal Towage Company boat number 88 going through a lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 169)
- Cushwa's Wharf, Williamsport, MD. From a series of photographs made by the Consolidation Coal Company, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 170)
- Arrival of the Cumberland. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 171)
- Dummy freighter and actors floating on Level 2 filming "Canals West" film. "C&O Canal. Lock 1, Georgetown, DC. Mrs. Romanowski, Con Heine's son, 3 actors and Captain Bender filming of transportation movie by University of Indiana." April 27, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 172)
- Lock and buildings. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 173)
- Lock and building. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 174)
- Towpath C&O Canal sketch. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 175)
- Foot bridge over canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 176)
- Some of the boatmen said that there was the ghost of an Indian chief who haunted the towpath at Big Pool east of Hancock, MD. Consolidation Coal Company pictures obtained in 1965 from Smithsonian Museum of History and Technology. Dr. John N, H. Hoffman, Curator. Photo of Big Pool, 1900-1920 (Box 20, Folder 177)
- Looking west on downstream side of Lock 52 toward Gonnoloway Creek aqueduct downstream of Hancock, MD. Shows partial clearing undergrowth and trees. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 178)
- Above Lock 52 in Hancock, MD back of railroad station. 200 feet upstream of bridge over Canal. Showing clearing of canal bed and towpath. March 16, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 179)
- Toll bridge over Potomac River at Hancock, MD.Old gate house, late 1800s (?) (Box 20, Folder 180)
- Old gate house along side of canal in Hanover. Winter, 1938-1939 %32882016916192 (Box 20, Folder 181)
- Lock 39 in Shepherdstown, WVA looking up stream after clearing of underbrush. March 16, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 182)
- Ferry Hill Platation opposite Shepherstown, WV. C&O Hike. April, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 183)
- Killiansburg Cave above Lock 38. Killing's Cave, on the banks of the Potomac, near Sharpsburg, the place of refuge of many citizens during the Battle of Antietam. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 184)
- Old mule barn at Four Locks. n.d., undated (Box 20, Folder 185)
- Dam number 3 near Harper's Ferry., 1938 (Box 20, Folder 186)
- Lock house 13 looking west on the C&O Canal before construction of Cabin John Bridge showing flume with rip rap. March 23, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 187)
- Two locks one in foreground the other in the background. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 188)
- Potomac Refining Co./Patent Lime Co. above Harper's Ferry on C&O Canal. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 189)
- Lock 44-Williamsport looking doewndtream clearing of underbrush on towpath below the lock. October 16, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 190)
- Monocacy Aqueduct dedication stone. South side of structure. Near Dickerson, MD. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 191)
- Monocacy Creek Aqueduct from east end. nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 192)
- Monocacy Creek Aqueduct from the west end. nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 193)
- Dam 4. July 22, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 194)
- Camp Kanawha. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 195)
- Point of Rocks, MD., early 1900s (Box 20, Folder 196)
- White's Ferry on the C&O Canal looking downstream from highway crossing below Lock 26 prior to clearing canal bed of undergrowth. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 197)
- Woods Lock 26 on the C&O Canal before clearing undergrowth from lock structure. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 198)
- Campbell's Lock 27 on the C&O Canal looking downstream from footbridge after clearing. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 199)
- Stone work. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 200)
- Patowmack canal. Great Falls, Virginia. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 201)
- Stone work. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 202)
- Stone work of lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 203)
- Stone work. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 204)
- Stone work of lock. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 205)
- Campbell's Lock 27 on C&O Canal looking upstream from footbridge prior to cleaning. December 3, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 206)
- Bruswick taken from lock looking upstream showing of structure after clearing of Canal bed. April 27, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 207)
- Catoctin Aqueduct near Lander, MD, pre 1973 (Box 20, Folder 208)
- Catoctin Aqueduct near Lander, MD. April 4, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 209)
- Catoctin Aqueduct. April 4, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 210)
- Catoctin Aqueduct. April 4, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 211)
- His lady leading (in light trousers), Justice Douglas, lags behind. Potomac in background., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 212)
- Ice skating on the C&O Canal. January 11, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 213)
- Hikers on the C&O Canal. Crew Cut Stewart Udall next to Mrs. Udall. May 6, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 214)
- Catoctin Aqueduct. November 1, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 215)
- Justice William O. Douglas near stop gate between locks 17 and 17. May 5, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 216)
- Brunswick, probably not lock house but possibility. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 217)
- Lock 28. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 218)
- Catoctin Aqueduct. April 4, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 219)
- Canal and lock near Harper's Ferry., 1880 (Box 20, Folder 220)
- Canal and lock 33 near Harper's Ferry., 1900 (Box 20, Folder 221)
- Lock 33 by-pass flume near Harper's Ferry, WV, undated (Box 20, Folder 222)
- Lock 33. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 223)
- Lock 33, Harper's Ferry looking upstream showing undergrowth prior to clearing. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 224)
- Lock 33, Harper's Ferry looking upstream showing undergrowth prior to clearing. December 2, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 225)
- Bicycling at lock 33 on the C&O Canal towpath near Harper's Ferry., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 226)
- Lock 33. n.d, undated (Box 20, Folder 227)
- Below Lock 51 looking upstream, below Hancock showing face of downstream side of lock after clearing. August 22, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 228)
- Canal boat on canal, possibly Lock 2, Washington DC. n.d, late 1800s (Box 20, Folder 229)
- Air view over Key Bridge with Rosslyn in the foreground and Georgetown in the background. Image reversed., ca. 1920 (Box 20, Folder 230)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge and Georgetown, Washington, DC, 1865 (Box 20, Folder 231)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge, Georgetown DC., ca. 1889 (Box 20, Folder 232)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge, Washington, DC, 1865 (Box 20, Folder 233)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge Washington, DC, 1870s (Box 20, Folder 234)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge Washington, DC, 1870s (Box 20, Folder 235)
- Aqueduct Bridge and Georgetown from the Virginia bank, c. 1860-1865, ca. 1860-1865 (Box 20, Folder 236)
- Alexandria Aqueduct prior to removal of piers in river., 1950 (Box 20, Folder 237)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge, northern arches and abutment Washington, DC, ca. 1889 (Box 20, Folder 238)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge, Georgetown., 1870s (Box 20, Folder 239)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge and ferry to Virginia. "At Georgetown the canal crossed the Potomac on a long wooden bridge, or aqueduct, built similar to a carriage bridge but instead of a roadway it had to support a box filled with water through which the boat sailed.", 1861-1865 (Box 20, Folder 240)
- Potomac Aqueduct Bridge, Washington, DC., ca. 1889 (Box 20, Folder 241)
- Paper from the President's Office of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 242)
- Papers from the President's Office of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 243)
- Paper from the President's Office of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 244)
- Paper from the President's Office of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 245)
- Official seal Type 2 of the C&O Canal Company, undated (Box 20, Folder 246)
- Official seal Type 1of the C&O Canal Company, undated (Box 20, Folder 247)
- Sketch for boiler and engine houses for pumps at Patterson Creek, MD on the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 248)
- Map of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 249)
- Map of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 250)
- Section of map of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 251)
- Section of map of the C&O Canal, undated (Box 20, Folder 252)
- Rowboat on the canal in front of boats, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 253)
- Medium format negative of canal barge in lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 1)
- Medium format negative of three men, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 2)
- Medium format negative of man with tricornered hat, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 3)
- Medium format negative of three men, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 4)
- Medium format negative of carts and boats. Different types of portage, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 5)
- Medium format negative of canal barge approaching lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Folder 21, Folder 6)
- Medium format negative of canal barge in lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 7)
- Medium format negative of canal barge in lock after water raised, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 8)
- Medium format negative of canal barge leaving lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 9)
- Medium format negative of bridge and canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 10)
- Medium format negative of bridge and canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 11)
- Medium format negative of Harpers Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 12)
- Medium format negative of canal barge "Chadakoyn" moored next to a wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 13)
- Medium format negative of canal barge being pulled by mules on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 14)
- Medium format negative of canal barge "Chadakoyn" moored next to a wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 15)
- Medium format negative of canoe at lock on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 16)
- Medium format negative of aqueduct on C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 17)
- Medium format negative of lock, lock keeper and lock keepers house on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 18)
- Medium format negative of aqueduct on C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 19)
- Medium format negative of aqueduct on the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 20)
- Medium format negative of canal barge Canal Towage Co. No.1, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 21)
- Medium format negative of canal barge and mules on aqueduct on C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 22)
- Medium format negative of bridge over flooded waterway, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 23)
- Large format negative of canal boat Canal Towage Co. No.3 on C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 18, Box 21, Folder 24)